翻译｜qweasdshilk　小愿8　　校对｜寓
字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
华盛顿
没 一切都好
Well, just great!
就是一些
No, not the presentation That's terrible.
白痴 撞上我了
Some idiot just hit me.
啊 你知道这要花多少钱
Ugh Do you realize how much this is going to cost
你赔不起 但是…
Not in money, which i have plenty of, but in...
什么鬼…
What the...
离我远点 滚开
Get away from me! Get away!
救命 来个人救我
Help me Someone help!
滚开
Stay away!
你在做什么
Ah! What are you doing
救命 救我
Look out! Help me!
神奇女侠 救我 带我离开
Wonder woman! Save me! Save me from them!
离开什么
From whom
恶魔 你没看见他们吗
Demons They're everywhere Don't you see them
我只看到了你
I see only one.
我问你最后一次
I'll ask you one last time.
你对我的家人都做了什么
What did you do with my family
史蒂文 是我 格洛里亚 我是你的妻子
Steven, it's me, Gloria! I'm your wife.
这些都是我们的孩子
These are our children.
你不是我的家人
You're not my family!
你杀了他们
You killed them, just like the others.
我要为他们报仇
Now it's your turn.
今晚没有人会死
No one's dying here tonight.
你不能这么做
It's not me you should be stopping.
他们是怪物
It's them Look at them!
你看清楚了吗
Look at them!
他们与我的邻居一样
It's just like the neighbors.
去我的小屋你会发现我是对的
Go to my shed You'll see I'm right!
你做了什么
What have you done
哥谭市
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
这不是我的错
It's not my fault.
我生了魔鬼这是魔鬼
I've given birth to the devil It's the devil!
你只是累了 把孩子给我
You're tired Give me the baby.
你也不想伤害她吧
You don't want to hurt her.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
正义大厅
犯下这些罪行的是守法公民
These crimes were committed by law-abiding citizens.
他们都说看到了恶魔
They all claim to have seen nightmare visions beforehand.
有什么线索吗
Any clue what's causing it
没有
No idea.
我就待一星期的班
The one week i fill in for Jordan,
结果就发生了这种事
and it couldn't be some hairy-ass monster
世界各地都有这样的情况
The same pattern is repeating around the world,
也许这是一个线索
so there could be an overriding factor.
也许是一个超自然事件
Perhaps a paranormal element.
你是说魔法吗
Are you talking about magic
我们以前碰到魔法 蝙蝠侠
We've come up against magic before, Batman.
薛西斯 鬼父 浮士德
Xerxes, trigon, Felix faust.
甚至连沙赞的力量也是来于魔法
Even shazam's powers are based in magic.
你有何高见
With as much as you've seen, can you rule it out
魔法只是一个借口
The criminally insane don't need magic as an excuse.
我建议我们还是多花点时间巡逻
I recommend spending more time on the streets
而不是一飞而过
instead of flying over them.
他的态度真友[恶]好[劣]
Hmm He's even friendlier than they say.
康斯坦丁
黑暗正义联盟
拉斯维加斯
五天前
谁定的狗屁规矩
Bollocks! In what bloody plane of existence does four of a kind lose
哎 康斯坦丁
Too, too bad, constantine.
希望你还有足够的赌资
Have you gained weight It looks good on you.
杰森 你应该一起玩几把的
What say you let your soul mate play a few hands, Jason
也许他你能改变我的运气
Maybe he'd change my luck.
他会让你玩的更尽兴点
He'd definitely be less mopey than you.
别听约翰·康斯坦丁胡扯
John constantine, the man who perfected the bad idea.
我来到这赌场是要找封印怪物
The only reason I came to this dung heap of a casino is to find a relic
的一件物品
to keep that monster locked away forever.
让我们一起玩 好了
Boys, boys! You're boring me Let's play, shall we
我的运气一直好得不的了
My luck's running as hot as me naughty bits.
好了 我们没多少时间了
Oh, but our next group of friends is due to arrive,
是时候结束了
so it's time to bust you out.
科波菲尔秀
Copperfield's coming Presto changeo!
一切尽在掌控
Woman in a box In a box.
说的没错
Yeah, he's classy, unlike you.
他们暗示的是不是那个大卫·科波菲尔
Are they implying David Copperfield, television magician, has true power
还拥有一堆岛屿还有克劳蒂亚·雪佛
Owns a chain of islands and dated Claudia schiffer What do you think
我只接受现金
No cards for me, and...
还有你输了 康斯坦丁
Oh, looks like you can't call my bet, constantine.
你输了
By my rules, you lose.
我加码
I raise.
用什么 你的灵魂可不值这么多
With what Your ratty soul ain't worth two bits.
不是廉价之物
Not two bits.
我要赌的是神秘房
I'm betting the house, the house of mystery.
我赌上了一切
And since I'm including everything inside,
阿比赞 看来你还有所保留
it looks like you're the one that can't call, abnegazar.
好吧 干不干
Well, what do you say, boys
来
I like the action.
我跟
I call.
就一个梦石 切
Really A chipped dream stone
我可拿出了
I'm out.
我的一切
Broken knick-knacks for the house of mystery and its contents
而你呢
Are you mad
我有灵魂捕手
I've got a working soul catcher.
奥兹之眼 还有garazi
That's ogid's eye spiker, eh And the garazi.
而且梦石可不是一个廉价物品 虽然他或许没什么用
So even if that very magical dreamstone doesn't work, it's still a big-ass Ruby.
看来我只好接受你的不平等条约了
I'd be a poor sport indeed if I didn't accept your fair wager.
看来 你输定了
Hell Now, that's a losing hand for the ages.
看吧 我…
Now, read them and...
什么
What
你们地狱是不是没有眼科医生
Do they have an eye doctor in hell
如果我是你 我会去就医
I'd make an appointment if I was you.
你耍诈
You cheated!
从技术上讲 我们都出了千 只不过我更高明
Technically, we both cheated I just did it better.
我要杀了你
I'll rip your bloody heart out!
这我借用下
Sorry, mate, I'm using that.
杰森你最好还是召唤你另一面来帮我
Situation here, Jason It's time to call your better half.
抱歉 约翰 你自保吧
Sorry, John, you're on your own.
康斯坦丁 我要把你烤熟 然后吃掉
Oi, I'm gonna roast your nuts and feed them to you, constantine.
人形去
Gone, gone, the form of man.
恶魔伊特莱根 来
Arise the demon, etrigan!
这首押韵的诗
Once more with words of metered rhyme
再次召唤伊特莱根
comes etrigan the slayer just in time.
我们是一伙的 对吗
Easy now, brother We're on the same side, right
我们握手言和吧
Let's use our words.
你们在搞笑吗 我们可是一伙的
Are you having a laugh We're the demons three.
杀
Kill everyone!
你会付出代价的 康斯坦丁
You will pay, constantine.
你的灵魂是我们的
Your soul will be ours.
很多白痴都这么说
Get in line, you prats.
康斯坦丁
Your ass is grass, constantine.
我们会报仇的
And we're the lawnmower.
既然战斗已结束
Since the battle's fought and won,
我也该走了
Jason blood with me is done.
五百年来 我都在想办法封印他
For 500 years, I've been bound to etrigan,
甚至摆脱他
fighting to keep him from coming forth,
而你强迫我召唤他
and you forced me to summon him.
不是什么都没发生吗
Everything got sorted.
他可能会疯狂杀戮
He could have gone on a killing spree.
而你不考虑成这些
You don't think You don't consider the cost.
是的 我没有
Yeah, I did.
但我当时危在旦夕
Weighed it against my being eaten alive and thought, "yeah, totally worth it."
你是一个超级混蛋 约翰
You're a world class bastard, John.
最终
And for my finale,
我会让这几头大象在我们眼前消失
I will make this terrible trio of terrifying tantors vanish before your eyes.
我希望那些大象活了下来
I hope those elephants survived.
你不会想要动物组织来找你的
You don't want peta on your back.
他们又不是真的
You're assuming they were real in the first place.
你还好吗 布鲁斯
How are you, Bruce
我很好 扎塔纳 就是忙了点
I'm fine, zatanna Busy.
你知道我在哪里可以找到约翰·康斯坦丁
You know where I can find John constantine
不知道
No.
你一定有办法
You must have some idea.
我们不保持联系
We don't keep in touch.
我知道你们两个有情史 所以我…
I know you two have history, so I...
小扎 蝙蝠侠需要约翰
Z, Batman needs to talk with John.
肯定是重要的事
You've got to come along, too It's important.
是你吗 波士顿
Is that you, Boston
是的
Yeah.
一切都是…
Everything is...
这家伙的精神真强大
Boy, this guy's mind is tough.
我坚持不住了…
Can't hold...
这是怎么回事
What is going on
去找约翰的路上在详说
I'll tell you on the way to John's.
但我要坐前面
Okay, but I call shotgun.
这地方联一个孩子都坐不下
I don't even think his kid could fit back here.
波士顿 你必须适应
Sorry, Boston, but life is for the living.
波士顿 就是那个马戏团演员
Boston brand He was a circus performer.
蝙蝠侠听说过我 告诉他我是他的粉丝
Batman's heard of me Sweet Tell him I'm a fan of his, too,
你明白怎么说的
but, you know, be cool about it.
是的 就是他
Yeah, that's him.
问下他有没有看过我的节目 他有一个受人欢迎的节目
Ask him if he caught one of my shows.He was a trapeze artist who loved being famous,
尤其受女性的欢迎
especially with the ladies.
男性就不一样了
Husbands, not so much.
你是在损我吗
You're killing me.
直到惹了一个不该惹的人
He had a knack for irritating the wrong people.
然后 大约五年前 报应来了
Then, about five years ago, Karma caught up with him.
在一个满席的周六秀上
It was a weekend show, full house.
波士顿被人枪杀了
Boston was in the middle of his death-defying act when...
他死了 本应当死了
He died, and that should have been that,
到了波士顿身上，事情却不一样了
but with Boston, things tend to get complicated.
女神罗摩给了他力量
His spirit was called by the goddess rama kushna.
让他得以精神状态存活
She took pity on him and gave him the power to possess the living,
这样他就可以行正义之事了
so he could bring his killer and others to justice.
嘿 我不想吹嘘 但我的技术真的很好
Hey, I don't wanna brag, but I'm good.
为什么他要像个小孩子一样在我墙上乱涂乱画
Why did he feel the need to write on my walls like a child
嗯 他很抱歉
Uh, yeah, he's sorry about that.
地址在哪里
Where is this address
GPS似乎今晚没什么有用
GPS doesn't seem especially useful tonight.
没有地址 神秘屋重来就不是固定的
It's not an address The house of mystery tends to move around.
之所以把信号放那
I didn't put the symbols in there for the GPS to find it.
是想要房子自己来找我们
I wanted the house to come to us.
她坚持不了多久 做点什么
She can't hold it Do something.
那里
There.
快进房子
Into the house!
小扎 你还好吗
Z, you all right
是的 只要你别压着我
Yeah, as soon as you get off me.
早知道你们要来这
I should have known you were the reason
我就不回伦敦了
I'm not back in London enjoying a pint.
看来房子更喜欢你一点
The house always did like you better.
你们三个在一起还真古怪
Odd trio for a road trip.
你们有何贵干
To what do I owe the visit
正义联盟认为最近的杀人事件可能是受魔法的影响
The league thinks that a recent spike in homicides may have a magical cause.
我都跟你们说过了
Told you something stinks.
现在是某些人有所保留
Now we know someone doesn't want us asking questions.
你已经有什么线索了
Looks like you've cracked it wide open, mate.
他说了什么
What did he say
你们还是自己说吧
Uh-uh I'm not playing telephone between you two.
他看到我了吧
We online
希望你的蝙蝠车
Great Sorry about the Batmobile.
购买了保险
I hope your insurance was paid up.
怎么 没有吗
What, is there even a policy for something like that
嗯
Mmm.
嘿 我告诉过你 不要这么做了 下次从门走进来行吗
Hey, I told you not to do that, orchid Use a bloody door.
我只是担心你
I am glad to see you are well.
这是新一任
How new is this one
不是
Not what you think.
她是这屋子的 灵
It's the magic of the house.
它想要跟人一样
Decided it wanted to experience humanity and gave itself a body.
它的确需要
It sure did.
精神存在 就像我一样
A spirit whose existence is not its own, like myself.
有意思
Interesting.
嗯 是的 我们是
Um, yeah, we are that.
老兄 你已经死了
Dead smooth you are, mate.
嘿 我有一段时间没
Hey, it's been a while, you know
拥有强大的魔法力量 还在生约翰的气
Powerful in true magic Angry at John.
这我知道
This, I understand.
但你仍对他有感情
Yet you still have feelings for him.
杀了他 还差不多
I could kill him.
你流露出痛苦
You exude pain.
你的生活是黑暗的 没有快乐
Your life is a patchwork of blackness with no time for joy.
你是怎么撑下来的
How do you cope with it
我有一个管家
I have a Butler.
这回答
That was enlightening.
嗯 我想我们应该聊正事了
Well, I guess we should have that chinwag about now.
- 恶魔  - 别
- Demons!  - It's not me!
我生出了魔鬼 我…
I've given birth to the devil. It's the...
这打破了命运之间的限制
Rama kushna says this will break down the walls between the planes.
甚至连来世也将受到影响
Even the afterlife will be affected.
是的 我马上去
Yeah, it's dodgy, all right I'll look into it.
我的意思是说 你们可以走了
Meanwhile, the house will drop you wherever you'd like.
哇 哇 哇 罗摩 你竟然说合作
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Rama says we have to work together.
来吧 这可是一个最牛的队
Come on! It's a dream team.
你 我 扎塔娜 蝙蝠侠 甚至正义联盟
You, me, zatanna, Batman, maybe even the justice league.
斗篷和紧身衣 对黑魔法没有作用
The capes and tights crew, useless against dark magic.
这就是为什么我们需要你带领我们
That's why we need you You can lead us.
波士顿 你要我们组团 而且还要我领导
Boston, do I strike you as a team player Much less a team leader.
问题是 就算是神也可能会出错
Point is, even deities can get it wrong.
所以我们才会得阑尾 还有 尼安德特人 电视真人秀
It's how we got the appendix, neanderthals and reality TV.
小扎 你帮我和他们说
Z, your help I could use.
好的 前提是我们成为一个团队
Okay, if we do it as a group.
这简直就是群尸玩过界
This is the monkey cage in sumatra all over again.
“哦 我们需要拯救这些猴子 ”她说
"Ooh, we need to save the monkeys," she said.
你这个混蛋
You're such an ass.
哦 不只是猴子
Oh, not the monkeys.
这话出自造成纽卡斯尔事件而且
Says the man who has newcastle and 100 other screw-ups on his resume,
还经常捅娄子的人之口
costing lives and souls.
但我至少没害死人
But not monkeys You're still way ahead on dead monkeys.
- 他们的往事  - 嗯
- They used to be a thing  - Mmm.
你只会让事情…
You just have to make things...
我们在浪费时间…
We're wasting time.
他死了 我接受这样的意外
He's dead, and I accept the risks,
所以我们能到达 还是你们两个需要时间
so can we get to it, or do you two need a timeout
十全十美让我们走在黑暗的一面
Fine and dandy Let's take a walk on the dark side then.
来吧 伙伴们
Coming, team
你不再是一个孩子 慢下来
Stop being a child and slow down.
我们要去哪里
Where are we going
里奇家
Ritchie's.
你最近和他说过话吗
Have you talked to him lately
我知道他很生气你不用提醒我 亲爱的
I know he's pissed You don't have to remind me, love.
这是我的经历 还记得吗
It's on my cv, remember
不 真的 他告诉你…
No, really, has he told you...
哦 不他快要死了
Oh, no He's dying.
约翰康斯坦丁
John constantine,
最后的救命稻草
purveyor of the dark arts and lifeline of last resort.
你朋友的灵魂我们一定会拿到手的
No matter Your friend's soul will be collected,
而你什么都做不了
and there's nothing you can do to alter that.
你们不如换一个地方玩吧
Why don't you go do something useful, like haunt a house
他在跟谁说话
Who's he talking to now
类似无常的东西
Shrouds They deliver souls to hell.
他们被你吸引了
They're drawn to you.
也许因为你身上的古龙水 batsy
Maybe it's your Cologne, batsy.
这个家伙从总是死里逃生
This one has cheated us many times.
真是令人烦恼
It is vexing.
嘘…
Boo.
这有点 但你们该走走人了
This has been lovely, but it's time for you lot to bugger off.
当时候到了 我一定会收走你的灵魂 康斯坦丁
When the time comes, I'll be the one to collect your soul, constantine.
是 是
Yeah, yeah.
我想我感觉到有一股能量力场
I thought I felt a disturbance in the force.
你过的怎样 约翰尼
How you doing, Johnny boy
扎塔娜和 蝙蝠侠
Zatanna and Batman
这到底是怎么回事
What the hell
进去再说
Tell you everything inside, mate.
可怜的家伙
You poor thing.
我上次骗了你
Yeah, I may have lied the last time we talked,
关于我的病情的严重程度
about exactly how fast I'm sledding downhill.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
重要的是你来了 约翰
But it means a lot you're here, John.
嘿 你不需要把说对不起 我原谅你了
And, hey, you don't have to say it You're forgiven.
但是 蝙蝠侠来我这做什么
Still wondering what Batman's doing in my living room.
我应该闭嘴是吗
And when is he gonna shut up, right
干嘛
What What's with the face
你不是来说对不起的 是吗
You're not here to say you're sorry, are you
当然 不是
Of course I am,
但我同时也想借卡香缇钥匙
but I was looking to borrow the keshanti key as well.
你…
Unbelievable.
我跟他说过了
I tried to tell him on the way.
是的 这不是你的错
Yeah, it's not your fault, z.
都是他的错
Just like everything, this is rock star Johnny's fault.
它发生的时候只有我和你 里奇
I was with you when it happened, ritchie.
我们肩并肩
We were side by side.
是的 是的 是的 肩并肩
Yeah, yeah, yeah, side by side.
我得了奇怪的魔法癌症 你而却扬名立万
But I got the weird magical cancer while you, you added to your rep.
不是吗
Isn't that right
听着 这是两码事
Look, me not making proper amends isn't related to the key,
而且 你也不需要了
which, truth be told, you're not gonna need, mate.
约翰
John!
最近这很频繁啊
Getting that a lot lately.
你自便 我不会帮忙的
You can go screw yourself I am not giving you crap.
我理解你的愤怒 但你
Your anger is understandable, but you need to reconsider.
要为大众考虑
Innocent lives are at stake.
好吧 医生说乐观的态度可以帮我改善病情
Well, doctors say an upbeat attitude can help,
而且重点是 我今天见到了蝙蝠侠
so what I'll focus on today is that I met Batman.
正义的力量
Force of good.
也很高兴见到你 扎塔娜
It was also nice seeing you, zatanna.
如果你们 没事了的话…
Now, if you'll excuse me...
就走吧
You can show yourselves out.
是他吗
This him
年度最佳父亲 现在给我命运之轮
Father of the year I'll need the gear now.
这怎么用
How does this work
它是一个魔法通道
It's basically a magical shortcut.
直接连接平行世界
It lets me access different planes of existence
而不用大费周章
without doing 20-odd hours of incantations.
现在 让我们看看 他经历了什么吧
In this case, I'll poke around this poor sod's memories to see how his madness began
更重要的是 为什么
and, more importantly, what caused it.
你们在这里做什么 我要去叫保安
What are you doing here I'm calling security.
我来确保这美眉不会坏事
I'll make sure the looky-loos stay out of our hair.
小扎 如果我这身体受到攻击 别忘了保护我
Z, give me a psychic shout if this body comes under attack.
我也可能被困在里面
Wouldn't do to be trapped inside, now.
你为什么非要一个人去
Wouldn't do to go in alone, and since I'm right here...
不行 太危险了
Too dangerous You're out of practice, love.
你当我来这
Look, you wanted me along I'm here.
是看戏的吗
I'm not waiting in the wings Let's do this.
小扎 你没事吧
Z You okay
我很好
I'm fine.
我不喜欢这里
I've never liked this sort of magic.
我能感觉到有黑暗要吞噬我
I can feel darkness seeping inside me.
我不知道你是怎么做的
How you stand it is beyond me.
如果你想出去的话…
It's all about control If you ever need a refresher...
我们讨论过了 我不会放弃的
We've had this conversation I haven't changed my mind.
那好 随你吧
Sure, sit out the war between good and evil.
毕竟 比你在马戏团的工作要好
After all, you've got a good thing going being applauded by mindless twits.
什么 现在说这个
Really Now
我认为我还是挺会挑时机的
Good a time as ever, I reckon.
- 敢顶嘴  - 不
- I'll teach you to talk back  - No!
我使用能让人们幸福的魔法
The magic I perform brings people happiness.
喝几杯不就行了
You sure it's not the two drink minimum, love
你真是一个悲观主义者
You're such a pessimist.
没错 所以我总是做好最坏的打算
Wrong I expect the worst, so I prepare for the worst,
那样我就有所准备了
and when the worst happens, I'm ready.
我却无法不改变什么
But my outlook doesn't alter the reality of the world.
“史蒂文 别喝了”
Steven, stop!
“别管我”
Leave me alone!
又一个美好时光
Another precious moment.
也有快乐
There was joy, too.
但他的痛苦把一切都驱散了
His madness swept it away.
谁做的好事
Who dropped the bed pan
就是现在
This is it This was the morning of his madness.
你认为是什么把他变成那样的
What do you think will set him off
我猜是数独
My guess is the sudoku.
把他逼疯的
He's got two 9s in the same row.
约翰
John.
跑 快跑
Run! Run! Run!
快跑 离开这里
Run! Let's get out of here!
老兄 你就不能减肥吗
Oh, come on, fellow Eat a piece of fruit, huh
该死的
Damn it!
这儿
Here it is.
我们必须离开这里
We've got to get out of here.
再等会
One more second.
快走 约翰 没时间了
Now, John There's no time.
到手
Got it.
哦 史上最臭
Oh! Shit's really hit the fan.
你一定要说出来吗 波士顿
You had to go there, Boston.
我们离开这里
Let's get the hell out of here.
嗯
Hmm.
我不知道这是什么 我也是
I don't recognize it Me, neither.
也许里奇知道
But if there's a person alive who can, it's ritchie.
你忘记了你才刚伤害他
Are you forgetting when you made your friend despise you
无所谓了 这事情太重要了
This is too bloody important for hurt feelings.
康斯坦丁
Constantine.
该死
Bollocks.
你是来见证你的…
You've arrived in time to witness my...
里奇
Ritchie!
回来 你这混蛋
Get back, you bastards!
约翰 先帮里奇
John, help ritchie.
看招
Take that! Boom!
没脉搏了
No pulse.
废话 还不想办法
We know! We know! Come on!
什么
Why
看来你挺有办法的
I see you have a few tricks of your own, eh
又不是所有的事都需要魔法
Not everything requires magic.
他醒了 的话 让他看下
Make sure he sees that right when he wakes up.
如果他醒的了
If he wakes.
我们需要谈谈 你和我
We need to talk, you and I,
要是你敢召唤召唤
but if you try and summon etrigan,
我就会在你念第一个词时就把你揍的说不出话
I'll fill your lungs with bile before the first verse is done.
明白吗
Savvy
其实情并非你们以为的那样
The situation was not how it seemed.
我到那就是那样的
The apartment was like that when I arrived Richard as well.
谁信你的鬼话
Come on! You were all over him.
我是在帮忙
I was attempting to help.
你们突然出现 我怕你们误会
When you burst in, i knew I'd get blamed, so I ran.
你相信他吗
Do you believe him
我相信他
Jason's not the murdery type.
他满脑子都是些骑士道德什么的
He's chock full of honor, loyalty, and rubbish of that sort.
为什么你在那里
Then tell us why you were there.
理查德收集的东西杂七杂八
Richard is known as a collector of the arcane and supernatural.
我想看看他那里有没有什么东西能带我来这
I wanted to see if he had something that could gain me access to this place.
为什么你要来这
Why would you wanna break in here
为了这个
For this.
构成了与邪恶相连的通道
The single most powerful conduit of evil in the history of the world.
虽被称为梦幻之石
He named it the dreamstone,
实际上却是恶魔之石
but it's really the stuff of nightmares.
那时我只是一个年轻的骑士
I was a young knight,green as grass.
对未来充满希望
With visions of battle-won glory dancing in my head.
但一切都变了
Needless to say, these were dispelled thoroughly.
他称自己为天命
He called himself destiny,
但梅林告诉我们他之前
but Merlin told us he was a man of science one time,
只是一个普通人
before he went insane.
他用魔法 灵魂铸造了梦石
Destiny forged the dreamstone with black magic and his soul.
用它去吸收人们的负面情绪
He used it to subject people to their most terrifying nightmares
壮大他的力量
and then feed off their torment.
那天是恶魔伊特莱根拯救的我们
It was actually the demon etrigan who won the day.
伊特莱根 去战斗
To battle, etrigan.
你杀了他 我就还你自由
Should you succeed, i will release you of your bond to me.
我答应你
If freedom is what's up for trade,
为了自由而战
then destiny's as good as slayed.
梅林 没这么简单就结束
You haven't won, Merlin This isn't over.
我发誓
I swear it.
梅林 履行你的承诺
Release me, Merlin, from your care.
我做了我该做的
My duty's done 'Tis only fair.
恐怕不行 我的朋友
I'm afraid that's not possible, friend demon.
我向你们道歉
I apologize to both you and Jason blood,
你们今后将共生死
but your future portends a shared destiny.
以此凡躯
Caught now, imprisoned in the form of man,
封印恶魔伊特莱根
I fix the demon, etrigan.
这同样是我
It was also the beginning
与伊特莱根的开始
of my eternal life sentence with etrigan.
没想到你放的这么随便
I didn't think you'd give it up willingly,
虽然它不是完整的
and though this piece is useless without the other half,
但仍有强大的力量
it's far from powerless.
这里非常安全
Safe enough where it is.
就这么随便放
Displayed like a tourist trinket in a Karachi bazaar
很神奇 不是吗
Neat, isn't it
神秘屋会保护我那些贵重的物品
The house keeps my valuables out of phase,
所以我不用担心
so they don't go wondering off.
这石头出现的过于巧合了
But, still, the timing of the stone's appearance and its power indicates
它肯定与这些事有关
that it's somehow involved with these crimes.
这就是为什么我把它放这了
Which is why it stays here, where only I can get to it.
我想我 我们反正所有人都知道你会把东西放哪
I think me, them, and everyone else who knows you might want it to be somewhere else.
他醒了
Your friend is awake.
里奇 是谁 是谁干的
Ritchie, who was it Who did this to you
浮士德
Faust.
费利克斯 浮士德你确定吗
Felix faust You sure
你在这啊 老混蛋
There you are, you old bastard.
我会把你揪出来的 菲利克斯浮士德
I give you wizard and asshole extraordinaire, Felix faust.
该死 我早该想到这混蛋
Hell, I should have put it together.
只有他会这么做
Conjuring a whirlwind is just his style.
联盟与浮士德斗过
The league had a run-in with faust,
但是他的位置并不在我们的数据库中
but his location isn't in our database.
恶魔又没有信用卡或社交媒体
Yeah, well, wizards don't make a habit of signing up for credit cards or social media.
当然能躲过你们
His grandly named observatory of the cosmos is hidden
却躲不过我
from the likes of you and superman, but not from me.
费利克斯 浮士德
Felix faust.
怎么回事
What's happening
形象的比喻 就是死机了
If this were a computer, I'd say it's frozen.
没戏
Cheers.
费利克斯 浮士德肯定用了防定位法术
Felix faust would take precautions against locator spells.
那就换个办法
There's another way,
但是有要去求人 还是讨厌我的人
but it involves asking a favor of someone that I don't have the best relationship with.
看来没人喜欢你 真令人震惊
Someone else dislikes you Shocking.
你朋友撑不了多久了
Your friend slips from the mortal plane.
约翰…
John...
那就帮他
Keep him alive and safe Understand
这不是我的职责
That is not my purpose.
我才不管这些
I don't give a flying shag what you think your bloody purpose is.
我命令你去帮他 付出你的一切
I order you to help him any and every way you're able.
我们走吧
Let's go.
好吧 我想问
All right, I'll ask.
为什么我们要来这
Why are we in the middle of a godforsaken swamp
因为亚历克荷兰在这
It's a favorite hidey hole of one Alec Holland,
他化身成了这里的植物
whose corpse was taken to be the most recent avatar of the green.
你们正联肯定没有这方面的记载
Bet you won't find that on your bloody cell phone.
我们的数据记载
Our data's more factual.
亚历克荷兰是被恐怖分子杀的 没有找到尸体
Alec Holland was murdered by terrorists His body was never recovered.
就这些
End of story.
其实没有
Not quite.
走开
Go away!
沼泽怪物
Swamp thing!
你不出来 我就把你烧出来
I know you're seeing this Get out here, or the posies get it!
约翰康斯坦丁
John constantine.
你敢以植物威胁我
You dare threaten the green.
老兄 你的社交能力真差劲
Dude, your social skills are horrendous.
别 我们来这 是因为一些重要的事
Please, we aren't here to harm any plants, but our need is urgent.
不要让约翰影响了你的判断
Don't let your feelings for John stop you from doing what's right.
你有一个花园
You have a garden.
是的 我在那放松 还每周浇水
Yes, I find it relaxing, and I water it every week.
我们需要找到一个人 他名叫费利克斯浮士德
We need to find a man, a wizard named Felix faust.
因你
A single human among your teeming masses.
我放下对约翰·康斯坦丁的仇恨
I only know John constantine because he enrages me.
浮士德住在一座无形的天文台
Faust lives in an observatory which is invisible.
我们不知道怎么去
It's a place where dark magic would infect the earth below it.
我带你们去那儿
I will take you there so you are no longer here.
到了
The place you seek is there.
那个地方我们进不去
That place is heavily warded.
我知道我们有过分歧 但这次你一定要帮我
I know we've had our differences, but we could really use your help.
全人类的命运就在我们手中
If we don't get a handle on this rotter, he'll threaten all of humanity.
为什么
What of it
你曾经是人类 就像我一样
You were once human, just like me.
那又如何
No longer.
也许他要做他所谓正义之事
Perhaps his actions are a kind of justice,
但人类就是正义的吗
for who destroys more of the green than your kind
他走了
And swamp thing has left the building.
有点难办
Guess we do it the hard way.
人身去
Or not Gone, gone, the form of man.
恶魔伊特莱根现身
Arise the demon etrigan!
搞什么…
What...
竟然敢
Who dares
我要把你
I, etrigan, bring down this house
埋葬 费利克斯浮士德
and build a tomb for Felix faust!
我可不会与恶魔战斗
As if I would stoop to brawling with a demon.
所以你还是与你的恶魔家人玩一玩吧
Fight others of your filthy kind.
我们都来自地狱但他们不是我家人
From hell though we may be, it does not make us family!
你喜欢这个设计吗
Do you like what I've done with the place
没有女人能在我这念咒语
No woman can speak in my sanctum sanctorum.
不，应该是所有人
I conjured it just for you and, of course, men everywhere.
对于一个演员来说 这可不是待客之道
As a fellow showman, this is no way to treat your guests.
给我下来
Now, settle down!
别打自己 停下
Stop hitting yourself Stop hitting yourself Stop hitting yourself.
不是所有问题都可以用你的玩具枪解决
Not everything can be solved with your peashooter.
你以为你死了我就拿你没办法了吗
Just because you're dead doesn't mean you're beyond my retribution.
是吗
Is that it
你该束手就擒的
Well, it's off to the old magicians home for you, mate Pudding night is Thursday.
我想看你把自己给烤熟 康斯坦丁
Try that fireball once more, constantine I'd love to see you cook your own goose.
让我
Let me...
收回我之前的话这玩具枪很有用
I take it back That thing is useful.
你在哪 亲爱的扎塔娜
Zatanna, where are you, darling
让我猜猜你在哪
I know you can't speak, but give me a wave.
你是唯一一个对我有威胁的
You're the only one here that's really a threat.
你在这啊
There you are This will sting a bit.
存储魔法 这可不够
Stored magic Really It's the TV dinner of spell casting, dear.
见识真正的魔法吧
Here's what real magic looks like.
小扎
Z!
小扎 不
Z, are you daft Stop!
我会杀了你的
I will kill you, woman!
小扎不
Z, don't!
你不能杀他
Don't kill him You can't.
滚开 约翰
Out of my way, John.
你的灵魂还是纯净的
If no blood is spilled, your soul is in the clear.
小扎 平心静气 就像我说的
Get control, z, just like I taught you.
吸气呼气
Easy-peasy, lemon squeezy Deep breaths.
放了他 亲爱的
Let it go, love.
我为什么不能像你一样释怀
Do you see why i can't do what you do
你只是失控了
You lost control is all Happens to the best of us.
你见过我失控 对吧
You've seen me in action, right
是的 一两次
Yeah, once or twice.
你们为什么这么对我 我什么
Why are you here I haven't done anything
坏事都没做
to warrant this kind of response.
这是不是你的
This yours
也许吧
I don't know Maybe I have several hundred rings
我有几百个这种样式的戒指
of varying design and properties.
不是他
It isn't him.
不是费利克斯 浮士德
Felix faust isn't the one behind the nightmare crimes.
他能召唤强大的恶魔
He summoned our old poker buddies in their more massive forms.
这什么意思
The hell does it all mean
意思就是他完全可以
It means Felix faust had access to the artifact whenever he wanted.
来攻击神秘屋
What artifact
好吧 一切白搞
Well, we're back to square one, then.
是吗 是你那位老朋友把我们引到这的
Unfortunately, no We were sent here by your friend, remember
里奇快死了
But ritchie's dying.
是吗
Is he
差点假戏真做
Boy, oh, boy I think I got closer to death than I planned.
不不不坏女孩
Ah! Nuh-uh-uh Bad girl.
我现在是你的主人
See, now, you were told to do everything to help me by the master of the house,
你要对我尊敬
and that does not include punching.
带我去我主房间
Bring me to the main room.
就这吧
I'll take it from here, beautiful.
但我现在需要你
But I need you out of my hair for now,
先去那里面呆会
so why don't you just go for a little walk
我们到了
Yeah! That's the stuff.
可为什么我们没在里面
Why aren't we inside
因为里奇现在控制着房子
Because ritchie's bloody well taken control of the house.
这就是报应
This is what you get for having mates.
波士顿 你能进去吗
Boston, can you get inside
不能
That would be a no.
里奇我不管你要闹咋样
Ritchie, you're gonna listen to me whether you like it or not.
先让我进去
Open the door.
你听到了吗 打开
Do you hear Open it!
你来太晚了 小约翰
Too late, Johnny boy.
里奇 不要
Ritchie, please!
收手吧 趁你还有良知
Stop while there's still time to save your soul.
这话竟从你口中说出
Says the man who skates away from everything.
因为你
Since you got me infected,
我只好满世界寻找解药 但终于被我找到了
I've looked all around the world for a cure and I've finally found it.
这块通灵的梦石
A small piece of the dreamstone It's sentient.
告诉我怎么把他拼全
It told me how to get the demons three to bring the rest of it to earth.
本来很简单的事
It would've been so easy to take it from them.
你却非要插一脚
Of course, rock star Johnny screwed everything sideways.
因此我就出此下策 并把你们的注意力引开
So we had to frame faust and get you to bring me here.
现在我成功了
Now I'm immortal and supercharged!
你被这块所谓通灵石给耍了
You've been played for a sap The stone isn't sentient.
是恶魔天命对你的利诱
What's left of destiny's soul was whispering sweet nothings in your ear,
以便于让他成就大业
getting you to commit atrocities to gain power and make his move.
你只是气我赢了
You're just pissed 'cause I won.
不是啊
I wish that were the case.
不可能
This can't be right.
不
No!
等等 等等 我们…我们有协议的
Wait! Wait! We.. We had a deal!
我们有协议的
We had a deal!
我等了五百年
Five hundred years, I've waited.
计划了五百年
Five hundred years, I've planned.
你看起来没变多少
Really I guess 500 must be the new 300.
要不我们喝一杯
What say we share your beauty secrets over a pint, eh
我没兴趣
A god does not prattle with mortals.
她还好吗
She gonna be okay
我…我不知道
I.. I don't know.
她的魔力用尽了
The amount of magic she's used,
一时不能恢复
sometimes you don't recover.
我不应该让她过这样的生活
I should have never led her back.
我真是一个自私的混蛋
Selfish bastard, I am.
事已至此
You've done what you can for now,
我们只能去阻止天命
but we have to stop destiny, or everyone's at risk.
他说的没错
He's right.
午夜前他就会成神
He'll have this city by midnight, the eastern seaboard by dawn.
到了那时就没有人能阻止他了
Then, what's to stop him He'll be a god.
有我一个混蛋就够了
We don't need another one of those mucking about.
好吧
All right.
阻止他们
Get them!
怎么阻止 他们无处不在
They're everywhere! Everywhere!
我宏愿将成
My will be done.
愚蠢 你怎么可能打败一个神
Fool! How can you hope to defeat a god
我能轻易的蹂躏你 你却连我的护盾都打不破
Not only can I sense you, you cannot defeat my shield.
神什么时候需要一个能量盾
Since when does god need a force shield
正义联盟在来的路上
The justice league are on their way.
他们不该来的
Suppose that couldn't be helped,
让他们远离他 不然他们
but make sure they stay well away from destiny,
会被影响的
to not be struck mad,
我可不想他们乱上加乱
unless you want a bunch of crazed super blokes ripping apart the city.
说的有点晚了 朋友
A little late for that, my friend.
约翰 你中了魔法
John, listen to me. You've been affected by magic.
现在就飞回太空”
Get away to space now.
杰森 又要你帮忙了
Sorry to have to ask this, Jason.
至少你还咨询了我的意见
At least you're asking.
人形已去
Gone, gone, the form of man.
恶魔起
Rise the demon etrigan!
又是你 康斯坦丁
So constantine calls once more.
你还真是麻烦
Just like a greedy, wanton...
等会再说
Save the bloody rhymes, and top that git!
令人扫兴
Killjoy.
伊特莱根 好久不见
I've had many years to think about you, etrigan.
称之为诗意的正义
Call this poetic justice.
该死
Holy crap.
看来你终于摆脱了诅咒
Looks like you've finally beat the curse, my boy.
虽然过程不是很美好
Wish it were under happier circumstances.
你在做什么
What are you doing
找人帮忙
Calling for help.
希望他不知道是我召唤的
I just hope he doesn't realize it's me doing the calling.
谁竟敢攻击我
Who dares strike at me
植物保护者 沼泽怪物
The defender of the green, swamp thing.
做的好
Perfect.
很高兴你没事 扎塔娜
Glad to see you back on your feet, zatanna.
无论你要做什么 赶快
Whatever you're gonna do, do it fast.
所谓的保护者
The so-called guardian of the green
却是为了人类
who secretly hopes to be human again.
让我矫正你的观念
Let me dispel you of that notion.
让你的心灵净化
Back to the dirt,
回到属于你的地方
where you belong.
他越来越强大了我们怎么办
He's getting more powerful by the second What the hell are we gonna do
我说我们去和他谈谈
I say we go and talk to a man about a horse.
你脑子坏了 胡说什么
Did you hit your head or something You're babbling.
一个特洛伊木马 波士顿来吧
A trojan horse, Boston Come on!
这里 废物
Over here, you wanker!
你这无耻的人类
You are puny and disrespectful.
让我看看你有什么本事
Let me see your madness.
看来对我这种人 你也没有什么办法
Well, that's the trouble with someone like me Been there, done that.
我赐你一死
I shall make you beg for death.
我可以求你别唧唧歪歪了吗
Can I beg you to stop talking
我的意思是你是个疯子 我才不会听疯子唧唧歪歪
I mean, all wizards are touched, but you, you're a full-blown nutter.
我要撕裂你的灵魂
I will tear your soul apart.
不是不屑和凡人闲聊吗
And what happened to not prattling with mortals, eh
怎么现在比我奶奶还啰嗦
You chatter like my grandma at a book club.
就是现在 波士顿
Now, Boston!
不给糖就捣蛋 怪物
Trick or treat, freak!
你是在跟我打招呼吗 还是你快死了
Is that a sword in your chest, or are you just glad to see me
梅林向你问候
Merlin sends his regards.
哦 顺便说一下 你输了
Oh, and by the way, you lose.
我会让你得逞吗
I don't think so.
约翰 我…
Johnny, I was...
你要救我
I was under a compulsion You've got to save me.
这是你欠我的 你欠我的
You owe me You owe me!
抱歉 老兄 天命不可违
Sorry, mate Can't take the chance that destiny is still pulling your strings.
约翰 救我
John, please! Help me!
救我 你这个混蛋
Help me, you bastard!
救我
Help me!
这场面可真让人不愉快
That was unpleasant.
我错过了什么
What the hell did I miss
小扎 你没事了 我还…
Z, you're okay I thought...
我头疼的就像宿醉了
My head feels like the morning after Brixton.
不至于这么糟吧
Surely not that bad.
所以我们自由了
So Merlin's spell hath ended.
没错
It would seem so.
事情要这么美满就好了
thought it's s good news sort of thing
- 怎么了  - 他之前没受伤
- What's going on  - Yeah He wasn't wounded.
也许是在他与伊特莱根捆定的那一天受伤的
Unless I miss my guess that happened on the dayhe was bound to etrigan.
现在我
And now that I'm not...
我无能为力 杰森
I'm truly sorry, Jason.
这是我希望的结局
Don't be It's a welcome end.
五百年来 我们同为一体
For 500 years, he and I have been bound.
我们种族不同
A demon from hell, a knight of renown.
不喜欢彼此
Though we were cursed to be slaves to each other,
离别才知我们心已系
I know of no man I'd want more for a brother.
安息吧
Farewell, mortal.
没有比他出生地更适
You couldn't have picked a better place.
合安葬他的地方了 他家就在不远
The villagewhere he was bornwas over there.was born was over there.
处 却只能以这种方式归家
Too bad it took this to get him home.
蝙蝠侠邀请我加入正联
Batman asked me to be in the justice league.
所以 你还在考虑
And you're considering it
我几天前去了那
I visited their headquarters a few days ago.
就像你说的那么有趣
It's interesting, and like you said,
也许是时做些改变了
maybe it's time to make a difference.
这你倒听我了
Listening to me now Uh-oh.
他们还邀请你
They want you, too.
是啊 没错
Good one, z Too right, they do.
你一定在开玩笑吧
You have got to be bloody kidding No way.
小蝙蝠侠一定会被我烦死的
Batty would go mental.
他邀请的你 而且你的反应如我所料
He was the one who asked, and I told him that's what you'd say.
保重 约翰
Be safe, John.
不 等下 等下
Now, hold on Hold on.
我拒绝的太仓促了
Maybe I've been a bit rash.
要不我们边喝边聊
Could you tell me more over a drink
就当庆祝新居
We could rechristen the house, as it were.
喝一杯
A drink
就一杯
Yeah, a drink.
别认为还会和上次一样
Don't think this is gonna turn into some sort of Manchester weekend.
别想
Get that out of your head.
但可以有一个特尔瑞德周四
We could have a trewhiddle Tuesday.
不可能
No, definitely not.
走的瞧
Well, let's mark that as a maybe.
亲爱的 这就是享受啊
Now, that's what I call making yourself useful, love.